Guide to the Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files, 1879-2007 (bulk 1910-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Library Addition Payments to Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, Architects, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
- Library Addition Taylor Alterations Material Sent To Architects, 1959-1964; (2 folders) (Box 13)
- Invitations To Bid, 1961; (2 folder) (Box 13)
- Contract Award, 1961 (Box 13)
- Change Orders - Library, 1961-1964 (Box 13)
- Library - Construction, 1962-1965 (Box 13)
- Construction, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
- Library Addition Furniture, 1960-1964 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Sculpture Gallery, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations General, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 14)
- [Library Addition - Payments to Geo. A Fuller Co. Contractor], 1961-1964 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Payments to Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, Architects, 1960-1963 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Payments To Contractor, 1961-1963 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations General, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Large Lecture Hall, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Invitations To Bid, 1961 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Specifications, 1961 (Box 14)
- Construction, 1961 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Change Orders, 1961-1964 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Contract Award Phase II, 1961 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Construction, 1961-1964 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Furniture, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
- Taylor Hall Alterations Sculpture Court, 1962-1963; (2 folders) (Box 14)
- Centennial Celebration (General), 1961 (Box 14)
- Command Performance, 1961 (Box 14)
- Centennial Celebration, 1959-1961; (2 folders) (Box 14)
- Contemporary Arts Conference, 1961 (Box 14)
- Academic Convocation, 1961 (Box 14)
- Centennial Mid-Nineteenth Century Festival, 1961 (Box 14)
- Alumnae Day, 1959-1961 (Box 14)
- Centennial Celebration Art Exhibition, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 14)
- Boots and Saddle Horseshow, 1960 (Box 14)
- International Conference, 1959-1961 (Box 14)
- [Centennial Celebration - Minutes], 1961 (Box 14)
- [Centennial Celebration - Reports to Trustees], 1959-1960 (Box 14)
- Main Building Alterations Payments to Goldstone and Dearborn, 1958-1961 (Box 14)
- [Main Building Alterations - Payments To Campbell Building Company], 1959-1961 (Box 14)
- Progress Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alterations Progress Photographs, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alterations General, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
- [Alterations To Main Building, Vassar College Specifications], 1959-1960 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alteration Program Goldstone and Dearborn Material Sent To The Architects, 1957-1960 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alteration Program, 1957-1958 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alterations, 1958-1959 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alterations Specifications, 1959-1960; (3 folders) (Box 15)
- Proposed Administration Building Receipts For Material Sent To Architect And Engineers, 1957 (Box 15)
- Invitations To Bid, 1959 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alterations Conference Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
- Change Orders, 1960-1961; (2 folders) (Box 15)
- Contract Award, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
- Contract Award Elevator, 1960-1961 (Box 15)
- Construction, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
- Proposed Administration Building General, 1954 (Box 15)
- Proposed Administration Building and Alterations to Main Building - Reports By Eero Saarinen, 1954-1955 (Box 15)
- Structural Repairs, 1959-1962; (6 folders) (Box 15)
- Furniture and Equipment, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
- Main Building Alterations Landscaping, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 15)
- Cooperative Bookshop, 1960 (Box 16)
- First Floor – Transverse, 1960 (Box 16)
- Main Building Alterations – 1st Fl. South Transverse Payments To Campbell Building Co., 1960 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility, 1981 (Box 16)
- [Walker Field House Survey – Muzak Of The Mid-Hudson Valley], 1982 (Box 16)
- Proposed Athletic Facilities, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- [Athletic Facility Contract], 1979-1981 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Change Estimates, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
- Walker Field House – Alarm System, 1982-1985; (2 folders) (Box 16)
- Walker - Audio Visual System, 1982 (Box 16)
- [Evaluation of Sound System Submittals For Walker Field House], 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Bleachers, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
- [Fuel and Electric Costs For Walker Field House – November 1982] (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Carpet (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Concrete Test Reports, 1981 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Electrical, 1981-1984 (Box 16)
- [Oildraulic Elevator Contract Data], 1981 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Equipment and Furnishings, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Finish Hardware, 1981 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility - Floor Covering, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility – Graphics, 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility HVAC and Shop Drawings, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Kitchen Equipment, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Landscaping, 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Lockers, 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Painting, 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Plumbing, 1983-1984; (2 folders) (Box 16)
- [Walker Field House Interior and Exterior Photographs, Wayne Soverns, Jr.], 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Photos, 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Plumbing Shop Drawings, 1983 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Roofing, 1981-1984 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility Seating, 1982 (Box 16)
- Athletic Facility - Security, 1983 (Box 16)
- Walker Field House - Sound System, 1982 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility Sprinklers, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
- Walker Field House - Squash Courts, 1984 (Box 17)
- Walker Field House - Storm Drainage, 1983 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility Subcontractors, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
- Specifications (Extras – Incomplete), 1981 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facilities Shop Drawing, 1981 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facilities Sprinkler Shop Dwgs, 1982 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility Swimming Pool, 1981-1984 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility Telephones, 1982 (Box 17)
- Physical Education Building, 1981-1984 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility – Job meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility Change Orders, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
- Athletic Facility Payments To Architect, 1981 (Box 17)
- [Athletic Building – Letters Of Transmittal and Various Correspondence], 1981 (Box 17)
- Installation Of Additional Steam Boiler [Payments To Burns and Roe, Inc., Invitations To Bid, Contract Award, Specifications and Plans.], 1962-1964 (Box 17)
- Improvements To Fire Protection System and Payments, 1962-1963 (Box 17)
- [Letters Of Requisition – Mylar Signs], 1981-1982 (Box 17)
- Laundry Building Conversion, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
- Chapel Alterations Construction, 1966-1968 (Box 17)
- Chapel Alterations [Change Orders], 1966-1967; (6 folders) (Box 17)
- Partial Consolidation Food Service Facilities General, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 17)
- Partial Consolidation Dining Facilities General, 1966 (Box 17)
- Consolidated Dining Facilities Goldstone and Dearborn Architect, 1965-1969 (Box 17)
- Chapel Organ, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
- Chapel Alterations E.W. Howell Co. Contractor, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
- Chapel Alterations General, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
- Chapel Alterations Architect, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
- [ Chapel Alterations – Specifications (Electrical, Plumbing, Heating and Ventilating)], 1966 (Box 18)
- Laundry Building Conversion Invitations To Bid, 1966 (Box 18)
- Laundry Building Conversion Specifications, 1966 (Box 18)
- Laundry Building Conversion, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
- Laundry Building Conversion Construction, 1966-1968 (Box 18)
- Laundry Building Construction Change Orders, 1966 (Box 18)
- Computer Center Contractor, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
- Computer Center Goldstone and Dearborn Architect, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
- Kuhn, Smith and Harris, Inc - Bid proposal, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 18)
- Dining Facilities #7 Model Photographs Quadrangle Project In Detail Josselyn-Jewett Project In Preliminary Form, 1967; (2 folders) (Box 18)
- Partial Consolidation Food Service Facilities General, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
- Invitations To Bid, 1966 (Box 18)
- Quadrangle Alterations and Dining Building Specifications, 1967 (Box 18)
- Consolidated Dining Facilities Change Orders, 1966 (Box 18)
- Proposed Dormitory Contract Award, 1957 (Box 18)
- Noyes House Executed Contract Documents, 1957; (4 folders) (Box 18)
- Noyes House – Construction, 1958-1959 (Box 18)
- Saarinen Dormitory – Statements Saarinen – Architect Post – Food Service Consultant, 1955-1958 (Box 18)
- Noyes House – Executed Contract Documents, 1958 (Box 18)
- [Vassar College and The Chase Manhattan Bank – Indenture of Mortgage and Trust Dated as of April 1, 1957] (Box 19)
- Noyes House – Subcontractors, 1957 (Box 19)
- Proposed Dormitory Receipts For Material Sent To Architect and Engineer, 1955-1958 (Box 19)
- Noyes House – Construction HHFA Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Proposed Dormitory (Saarinen), 1955-1959; (3 folders) (Box 19)
- Proposed Dormitory (Saarinen) Photographs Of Model, 1959 (Box 19)
- [Vassar College Contract Documents – New Dormitory Project No. NY 30-CH-43 (D) (Office Copy)], 1957 (Box 19)
- Noyes house Furnishings – Statements Eero Saarinen and Associates, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Noyes House – Quarterly Reports Status of Construction, 1957-1959 (Box 19)
- Noyes House – Construction, 1957-1958; (5 folders) (Box 19)
- Noyes House – Payments To Gilbane Building Co., 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Noyes House Construction Change Orders, 1958 (Box 19)
- Noyes House – Food Service Noyes House Cushing House Kitchen Alterations, 1957-1959 (Box 19)
- Cushing House Kitchen Alterations Contract Award and Construction, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
- Cushing House Kitchen Alterations Change Orders, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
- Cushing House Kitchen Alterations Specifications, 1958 (Box 19)
- Cushing House Kitchen Alterations Payments To Gilbane Building Company, 1958; (4 folders) (Box 19)
- Noyes House Food Service – Cushing House Kitchen Alterations Payments To Goldstone and Dearborn, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Ferrell House Payments Made To Goldstone and Dearborn, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Ferrell House Payments To John G. Pearse Contractor, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Ferrell House (Chaplain’s Residence) Goldstone and Dearborn, Architects, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Ferrell House – Working Specifications, 1957 (Box 19)
- Ferrell House – Construction, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
- Allis Chalmers Unit Substation Specifications, 1955 (Box 19)
- DC To AC Conversion, 1937 (Box 19)
- [G. E. Substation Specifications], 1955 (Box 19)
- [Westinghouse Substation Specifications], 1955 (Box 19)
- DC-AC Conversion Substation Contract Award, 1955-1956 (Box 19)
- [Allis-Chalmers Substation Instruction Book], 1955 (Box 19)
- Power Plant – DC To AC Conversion Sub-Station, 1954-1956 (Box 20)
- DC To AC Conversion Sub-Station Preliminary Specifications [and Bids Received], 1955 (Box 20)
- DC To AC Conversion Distribution System Contract Award, 1956 (Box 20)
- [Allis-Chalmers Power Transformer Manual], 1955 (Box 20)
- [Specification For The Installation Of The Outdoor Unit Substation For Vassar College (With Drawing)], 1955 (Box 20)
- [Specification For The Installation Of The Outdoor Unit Substation For Vassar College (With Notice To Bidders)], 1955; (5 folders) (Box 20)
- [Burns and Roe Inc Daily construction Reports], 1956; (3 folders) (Box 20)
- DC To AC Conversion – Phase II Payments To Hatzel and Buehler, Inc., 1956 (Box 20)
- Distribution System – Phase II Contract Award, 1956 (Box 20)
- Distribution System – Phase II Specifications – Proposal Forms, 1956 (Box 20)
- [Specification For The Electrical Distribution System, Phase II For Vassar College], 1956 (Box 20)
- DC To AC Conversion Distribution System Invitations To Bid, 1955 (Box 20)
- Specification For The Electrical Distribution System, Phase II For Vassar College (Proposal Filled In 67 Watson-Fiage), 1956 (Box 20)
- [Specification For The Electrical Distribution System, Phase III for Vassar College (File Copy)], 1957 (Box 20)
- DC To AC Conversion Payments To Burns and Roe, Inc., 1955-1960 (Box 20)
- Power Plant – DC To AC Conversion Receipts For Materials Sent To Engineers, 1954-1955; (2 folders) (Box 20)
- Power Plant – DC To AC Conversion Distribution System, 1941, 1955-1960 (Box 20)
- DC To AC Conversion Distribution System – Buildings (General), 1956-1958 (Box 20)
- Payments To L. Yanko, Inc. Construction Work – Phase III, 1957 (Box 20)
- Payments To Hatzel and Buehler, Inc. Electrical Work – Phase III, 1957 (Box 20)
- Distribution System – Phase III, 1956-1957 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase III Specifications, 1957 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase III Contract Award, 1957-1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase III Hatzel and Buehler, Inc. – Contract and Change Orders, 1957-1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase III L. Yanko, Inc. – Contract and Change Orders, 1957 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase III L. Yanko, Inc. – Progress Reports (Contract Award), 1957 (Box 21)
- Payments To L. Yanko, Inc. Construction Work –Phase IV, 1958 (Box 21)
- Payments To Hatzel and Buehler, Inc. Electrcial Work – Phase IV, 1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV, 1957-1959 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV Invitations To Bid, 1958 (Box 21)
- [DC To AC Conversion –Distribution System Phase III Contract Drawing Correspondence], 1957 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV Specifications, 1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV Equipment Contract Award, 1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV Hatzel and Buehler, Inc – Contract and Change Orders, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV L. Yanko, Inc. – Contract and Change Orders, 1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System – Phase IV Contract Award – Contractors General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 21)
- Power Plant Survey, 1957-1960 (Box 21)
- [Report on Review of Boiler House Auxiliaries For Conversion To AC Operation Future Steam Loads and Future Fuel For Vassar], 1958 (Box 21)
- Distribution System Phase V Specifications and Invitations To Bid, 1959 (Box 21)
- Distribution System Phase V Quotations, 1959 (Box 21)
- Contracts – Phase V, 1959 (Box 21)
- Payments To Hatzel and Buehler, Inc. Phase V, 1959; (2 folders) (Box 21)
- Chicago House Payments To Campbell Building Co. Contractor, 1958 (Box 21)
- Language Building (Proposed) (Schweikher), 1957 (Box 21)
- Chicago House (Language Building), 1958 (Box 21)
- Proposed Language House (Schweikher), 1956; (6 folders) (Box 21)
- Language Building Invitations To Bid, 1957-1958 (Box 21)
- Chicago House – Construction, 1958 (Box 21)
- Language Center – Roofing Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
- Chicago House – Construction, 1958 (Box 21)
- Proposed Language House (Schweikher), 1954-1956 (Box 22)
- Chicago Hill – Change Orders, 1958-1959 (Box 22)
- Chicago House – Change Orders, 1958 (Box 22)
- Language Building – Audio Visual, 1958-1959 (Box 22)
- Chicago House – Audio Visual, 1958; (2 folders) (Box 22)
- Language Building – [Invitations to Bid, Audio Visual, Equipment and Illustrative Material], 1958 (Box 22)
- Language House Payments To Schweikher and Elting, 1958-1959 (Box 22)
- Language Building Audi Visual Specifications, 1958 (Box 22)
- Chicago House Furnishings, 1958-1959 (Box 22)
- [Purchase Order For Language Center, Campbell Building Co. Inc], 1958-1959 (Box 22)
- [Language Center For Vassar College Copies Original Invoices For Financial Accounting], 1958-1959; (2 folders) (Box 22)
- [Payroll Abstract For Language Center Construction, Campbell Building Co. Inc], 1959 (Box 22)
- Chicago Lab – O+M Manuals, 1986 (Box 22)
- Chicago Hall – Punch List, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
- Chicago – Lang. Lab. Specifications, 1985 (Box 22)
- Chicago Hall Language Lab, 1965-1974; (4 folders) (Box 22)
- Chicago Hall – Roof Antenna, 1985 (Box 22)
- [Specifications For The Alterations To The Language Laboratory Chicago Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, New York], 1985 (Box 22)
- Chicago Hall and Hardware and Hollow Metal, 1985 (Box 23)
- Chicago – Lang. Lab – HVAC OandM Manual, 1985 (Box 23)
- Chicago – Lang. Lab ’85 – Bids, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
- Chicago Hall Conference Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
- Chicago – Contracts and Change Overs, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
- Chicago Hall - New Language Lab, 1985 (Box 23)
- Chicago Hall Renovations, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
- Survey of Underground Distribution System Engineers, 1964-1971 (Box 23)
- Underground Steam Distribution System Phase I Shaker, Travis and Quinn, Inc., 1965 (Box 23)
- Underground Steam Distribution System Phase II Shaker, Travis and Quinn, Inc., 1966 (Box 23)
- Underground Steam Distribution System Phase III Shaker, Travis and Quinn, Inc., 1967 (Box 23)
- Underground Distribution System Invitations To Bid, 1965 (Box 23)
- Survey of Underground Distribution System, 1964-1965 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Construction, 1965 (Box 23)
- Underground Distribution System – Specifications, 1964-1965 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Phase II, 1966 (Box 23)
- Underground Distribution System – Specifications Phase II, 1966 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Phase II Invitations To Bid, 1966 (Box 23)
- Underground Steam Distribution System Phase II Change Orders, 1966 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Phase III, 1967-1969 (Box 23)
- Steam Line Replacement Alum. Hse. –Collegeview Ave. Area Shaker, Travis and Quinn, Inc., 1969 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Phase IV, 1979 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Phase IV Specifications, 1968 (Box 23)
- Steam Distribution System Phase V, 1969 (Box 23)
- Contracts – Phase V The Nash Engineering Company, 1959; (2 folders) (Box 23)
- Raymond Avenue Steam Line Replacement, 1971, 1973-1981 (Box 23)
- Engineering Survey Of Utilities System, 1966-1968 (Box 23)
- Survey Of Utilities System Engineers Burns and Roe, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 23)
- Boiler Plant Conversion Contract Award, 1968 (Box 23)
- Boiler Plant Conversion To Oil and Gas Firing Engineers – Burns and Roe, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 23)
- Boiler Plant Conversion To Oil and Gas Firing Contractor – Shaker, Travis and Quinn, 1968-1969; (3 folders) (Box 23)
- Boiler Plant Conversion To Oil and Gas Firing General, 1968 (Box 23)
- Specifications [Boiler Plant Conversion], 1968 (Box 23)
- [Boiler Plant Conversion Invitations To Bid], 1968 (Box 23)
- [Bid Covering Coen Burners], 1968 (Box 23)
- [Boiler Plant Conversion C. N. Flagg and Co. Inc Bid], 1968 (Box 23)
- [Boiler Plant – Shot Drawings, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, New York], 1968 (Box 23)
- [System Function and Operation Manual For Vassar College Boiler Plant Poughkeepsie, NewYork], 1969 (Box 23)
- 13.8 kv Electrical Distribution System General, 1973; (2 folders) (Box 24)
- Electrical 13.2kv Power Distribution System, 1969-1970 (Box 24)
- Boiler Plant Conversion Construction, 1968 (Box 24)
- 13.2 kv Electrical Distribution System Switchgear Specifications, 1969-1974 (Box 24)
- 15kv Allis Chalmers Switchgear Instruction Manuals, 1971-1972 (Box 24)
- Bids For 13.8 kv Electrical System, 1971 (Box 24)
- Frank H. McEnaney, Inc. – Contractor 13.8 kv Elec. Distribution System, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
- Specification S2731-1 Additions To Electric Distribution System and Other Utilities, 1971 (Box 24)
- 13.8 kv Electrical Distribution System Shop Drawings Frank H. McEnaney, Inc., 1972 (Box 24)
- Sewer (Box 24)
- Sewer District Right Of Way – Vassar Lake, 1958-1959 (Box 24)
- [Sewer District Town Of Poughkeepsie], 1954-1970 (Box 24)
- [Arlington Sewer District Town of Poughkeepsie Sewer System (Vassar College Outfall) Final Specs], 1956 (Box 24)
- [Specifications For The Construction Of Sewers (Review Copy)] (Box 24)
- Town Water Improvement Area, 1969-1976 (Box 24)
- Town Water Main, 1974 (Box 24)
- Water Line From Town Water Main, 1970-1972; (5 folders) (Box 24)
- Water Supply V. C. Of Historical Value Only, 1905 (Box 24)
- [Vassar College Water Tank Removal], 1925-1973 (Box 24)
- Avery Hall Alterations Cost Consultants Wood and Tower, Inc., 1972 (Box 24)
- Avery Hall Alterations Report On Expenditures, 1972 (Box 24)
- Avery Hall Alterations Architect Robertson Ward, Jr., 1972 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop (Power House Conversion) Report On Expenditures, 1972-1975 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop Architect (Power House Conversion) Robertson Ward, Jr., 1971-1974 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop Contractor Eberhard Builders, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop (Power House Conversion) Cost Consultants Wood and Tower, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop Fairway Testing Company, 1972 (Box 24)
- Theater Project, 1971-1972 (Box 24)
- Theater Project Drama Workshop (Powerhouse Conversion), 1972 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop, 1972-1977 (Box 24)
- Drama Workshop Concrete Test Reports Fairway Testing Company, 1972 (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop Photos, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop Sound System, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop Change Orders, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop Contract Documents, 1972; (2 folders) (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop Bids, 1972 (Box 25)
- [Drama Workshop – Theatre Equipment Purchased by V. C.], 1972; (2 folders) (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop – Misc. Shop Drawings, 1972 (Box 25)
- Misc. Metals, 1973 (Box 25)
- Plumbing, 1972 (Box 25)
- Steel, 1972; (2 folders) (Box 25)
- Ventilating and Air Conditioning, 1972 (Box 25)
- Transmittals Drama Workshop, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop – HVAC, Plumbing Manual (Box 25)
- Electric, 1972 (Box 25)
- Drama Workshop – Transformers, 1972 (Box 25)
- Heating, 1972 (Box 25)
- Experimental Theater General, 1965-1968 (Box 25)
- Experimental Theater, 1965 (Box 25)
- Experimental Theater Architect John M. Johansen, 1965-1968 (Box 25)
- Experimental Theater Borings, 1966-1967 (Box 25)
- Subcommittee for Experimental Theater, 1968 (Box 25)
- Specifications and Invitations To Bid, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 25)
- [Performing Arts], 1970 (Box 25)
- [Specifications For The Construction Of Experimental Theatre, Vassar College], 1967 (Box 25)
- Computer Center Alterations, 1969 (Box 25)
- Computer Center, 1965-1974 (Box 25)
- [Vassar College – A Program For Data Processing], 1964 (Box 26)
- [Vassar College – An Analysis Of The Data Processing Requirements For Education and Research], 1965 (Box 26)
- [Proposal To NSF For Financial Aid For Purchasing of IBM 360/30 – D Computer], 1966 (Box 26)
- Computer Center Proposal For NSF Assistance, 1965 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Concrete Test Reports (Fairway Testing Co.), 1972; (3 folders) (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Reports On Expenditure, 1972-1979 (Box 26)
- Cost Consultants – Biological Sciences Building, 1968-1970 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Fairway Testing Company, 1972 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Contractor J. B. Primiano and Son, 1972-1978 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building, 1965-1978 (Box 26)
- Biological Science Building Architect Sherwood, Mills and Smith, 1966-1976 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building General, 1969-1977 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building (Proposed), 1958-1964 (Box 26)
- [Biological Sciences Building – Departmental Requirements], 1966 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Job Meeting Memoranda, 1966-1973; (6 folders) (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Equipment, 1971 (Box 26)
- Biological Sciences Building Furnishings, 1973; (5 folders) (Box 27)
- Biological Sciences Building Hardware Schedule, 1971 (Box 27)
- Biological Science Building HEW Monthly Construction Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
- Biological Sciences Building Photos, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
- Biological Sciences Building – Photos Site Model Volume Studies, 1967 (Box 27)
- Biological Science Building Test Borings, 1968 (Box 27)
- [Biological Science Building Contractors], 1973-1977; (2 folders) (Box 27)
- [Photos – Biological Sciences Building], 1970 (Box 27)
- Specifications, 1971-1972 (Box 27)
- [Biological Sciences Building Specifications], 1971 (Box 27)
- [Biological Sciences Building – Site Work Specifications and Addendum], 1972 (Box 27)